Prophet T.B. Joshua's Visit To The Holy Land - Jerusalem & The Sea Of Galilee
In Matthew 4, Jesus went about all Galilee, teaching in their synagogues, preaching the gospel of the Kingdom
and healing all kinds of sickness and disease among the people.
After these things, Jesus went out over the Sea of Galilee, which is the Sea of Tiberias.
As he walked by the Sea of Galilee, he saw Simon and Andrew, his brother, casting a net into the sea
for they were fishermen.
Then Jesus said to them, "Follow me and I will make you fishers of men".
They immediately left their nets and followed him.
When he had come into Jerusalem in John 21, all the city was moved, saying, "Who is this?"
So the multitudes said, "This is Jesus, the Prophet from Nazareth of Galilee".
And this is Prophet T.B. Joshua's visit to Jerusalem and the Sea of Galilee - a visit to the Holy Land.
Visit of Israeli Ambassador Guy Feldman & ZAKA's Rabbi Yehuda Zahav To Prophet T.B. Joshua
Upon hearing of the support of Prophet T.B. Joshua to the nation of Israel, the Israeli Ambassador to Nigeria
Guy Feldman visited Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Visit of Israeli Ambassador Guy Feldman & ZAKA's Rabbi Yehuda Zahav To Prophet T.B. Joshua
In those days, Jesus came from Nazareth of Galilee and was baptised by John in the Jordan.
And when he came up out of the water, immediately he saw the heavens opened
and the Spirit descending upon him like a dove, and a voice came from Heaven,
"Thou art my beloved Son; with thee I am well pleased". In Mark 1: 9-11.
From this very valley, a call to visit, which is T.B. Joshua.
Idan Grinbaum - I am the Mayor of the Jordan Valley Regional Council.
Hello, T.B. Joshua!
On behalf of myself and all the people of the Jordan Valley Regional Council,
I am more than happy to invite you, to come over and visit my place.
I would love to show you what is going on, around the Sea of Galilee.
Maybe we can do something together, to make our communities closer.
I'll be expecting you; thank you very much.
A call from Tiberias from the home of the families of Jesus of Nazareth and His disciples
Simon, Andrew, Peter, Philip, Bartholomew, James and John.
Prophet T.B. Joshua receives an invitation to visit.
My name is Joseph. I am the Mayor of Tiberias.
It is actually Joseph Ben David 'Son of David'.
I am the Mayor of Tiberias, the Sea of Galilee.
I would like to invite you to Tiberias and the Sea of Galilee.
We are more than delighted to meet you next week here in Israel,
in the Holy Land, at the Holy Lake here in Tiberias.
I'd be very glad to meet you, thank you.
Prophet T.B. Joshua's Visit To The Holy Land - Jerusalem & The Sea of Galilee
Prophet T.B. Joshua was invited to Israel to meet with important dignitaries such as the Mayor of Jerusalem,
the Mayor of Tiberias,
the Mayor of the Jordan Valley,
the Deputy Mayor of Jerusalem,
the Foreign Affairs & Media Advisor to the Mayor of Jerusalem.
Prophet T.B. Joshua's Visit To The Holy Land
Accepting their invitations, Prophet T.B. Joshua travels to the Holy Land - Jerusalem and the Sea of Galilee.
His first visit is to the Jerusalem Municipality to meet with the Mayor of Jerusalem, Mayor Nir Barkat.
Welcomed by the Foreign Affairs Advisor Frayda Leibtag.
How are you, Prophet Joshua?
Welcome to my city - our Holy City.
Please come in.
Please sit.
Mayor of Jerusalem Nir Barkat Hosts Prophet T.B. Joshua At His Office In Jerusalem
Prophet Joshua, you give us a lot of honour.
Thank you.
The connection between you, Jerusalem and ZAKA is in many ways a connection of holiness
and this connection is very important to me.
Thank you.
I wanted to share that with you and thank you for your involvement and help.
I am at your honour and service. I am very happy that you came by.
Thank you.
Anything, Yehuda, I can do to bond the relationship.
anything I can do to help you, please tell my team.
I will maintain the relationship according to your mission and my mission.
Amen.
Thank you very much.
Mayor of Jerusalem Nir Barkat Hosts Prophet T.B. Joshua At His Office In Jerusalem
Jesus fed the 5,000, walked on water and calmed the winds and waves in this very region.
Prophet T.B. Joshua visits the Mayor of Tiberias, Joseph Ben David.
It is a great honour for us that you came here.
Thank you for taking your time.
I should come and tell you about Tiberias and the Sea of Galilee.
Mayor of Jerusalem Nir Barkat Hosts Prophet T.B. Joshua At His Office In Jerusalem
My name is Joseph Ben David. It’s actually ‘Joseph Son of David’. I am the Mayor of Tiberias.
Thank you.
Thank you, I am meeting my brother today.
Welcome. Thank you very much.
I am more than excited to meet Prophet T.B. Joshua and his delegation.
Of course, I would like to take this opportunity to invite all the Emmanuel TV viewers
to come here to the Sea of Galilee.
See the blue area, here is the Sea of Galilee.
Come here to Tiberias in Israel!
We would like to host you and have you come to this beautiful land of miracles.
Keep watching Emmanuel TV!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Arrives At The Sea Of Galilee By Helicopter to Meet The Mayor Of Jordan Valley
An Israeli Television Station Awaits The Arrival Of Prophet T.B. Joshua To The Sea Of Galilee
Prophet!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Is Welcomed By The Mayor Of The Jordan Valley Regional Council
Thank you very much for coming to the Sea of Galilee.
Thank you, Mayor. I am happy to meet you.
I appreciate that you came all the way from Nigeria.
I have heard so much about you.
Thank you very much. Let's go inside.
Welcoming Prophet T.B. Joshua to the historic and biblical region is Mayor Idan Grinbaum.
The Mayor of the Jordan Valley ushers the Man of God to Beit Gabriel, to the peace room -
a historic room where peace was reconfirmed between Jordan and Israel during a 1994 meeting
with Israeli Prime Minister Jitzchak Rabin and Jordan's King Hussein.
Awaiting him is an Israeli TV Station that takes the opportunity to have an exclusive interview
with Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Pastor Joshua, may I ask, you are known as a Prophet; what is your prophecy for this land?
That is why we are here.
Are we going to have war or peace?
No, don't worry, that is why we are here.
We are here.
Whatever life brings, I will be here with you.
So, we are protected now?
By the grace of God.
Can you tell us in a few sentences, how did you get your power?
From my Father, Jesus, who was born in this land.
I am an inheritance of His grace - the grace of Jesus Christ.
What was your first prophecy?
It is not my prophecy; it is God's prophecy.
You cure people by chasing the devil or demons out of them;
are demons here also in this land?
Demons are responsible for the pain, killing, stealing and destruction.
My purpose of praying for people is to give them relief,
to separate them from the demons that are responsible for the pain and affliction.
Mayor Of The Jordan Valley Idan Grinbaum Hosts Prophet T.B. Joshua At The Sea Of Galilee
Once again - thank you very much.
My name is Idan Grinbaum, and I am the Mayor of the Jordan Valley Regional Council.
I appreciate it very much and it is a great honour to have Prophet T.B. Joshua near me.
I want to invite everybody to visit this beautiful place - the Sea of Galilee.
Join us here to see this beautiful and holy place; I will be expecting you.
I want to say, this is my great day being in the city of the Lord Jesus -
walking where He had walked during His earthly ministry.
I am honoured.
I am at home.
Thank you very much. God will reward you.
Thank you very much. You are our brother and special guest.
We are really honoured to have you here with us.
My name is Idan Grinbaum. Keep watching Emmanuel TV!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Visits Beit Gabriel At The Southern Tip Of The Sea Of Galilee
After the meeting, Prophet T.B. Joshua tours the facilities at Beit Gabriel.
During the tour, Prophet T.B. Joshua visits the Voice of Hope radio station at Beit Gabriel.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Visits The Voice Of Hope Radio Station At Beit Gabriel
Hi! I am Gary Hull, the General Manager of the newest radio station in Israel.
It is the Voice of Hope for all the Middle East.
Today we are so glad to be able to walk together with Prophet Joshua in the land of Jesus.
It is so good to know that he is continuing to broadcast the Word of God on Emmanuel TV.
Thank you for watching Emmanuel TV, stay tuned and be blessed!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Is Flown By Helicopter Over The Dead Sea To The Judean Desert
Flying over the Southern Judean Desert, Prophet T.B. Joshua visits the ancient fortress at Masada,
overlooking the Dead Sea.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Arrives At Masada - An Ancient Fortress And World Heritance Site In Southern Israel
Prophet T.B. Joshua Kneels To Pray In the Judean Desert
As Prophet T.B. Joshua kneels to pray, we remember the scriptures in Luke 5:16.
So Jesus Himself often withdrew into the wilderness and prayed.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Kneels To Pray In the Judean Desert
RV: Mel Flowers 21/03/2019